nderf.org 2013-05-24

# Privacy

### Web Site Privacy Information

#### NDERF

recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site:  http://www.nderf.org. The Site is operated by  Experience Research Foundation.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at  or by postal mail to:

  * NDERF
  * P.O. Box 20238
  * Houma, LA
  * 70360

Identifying Information. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us in our research capacity or to answer questions. Generally, NDERF requests identifying information when you: 

  * Register for the forum on any of our web sites. 
  * Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion. 
  * Participate in filling out our research questionnaires. 
  * Request a SPECIAL SERVICE
  * Request information, contact, or from technical support or customer service.

In these instances, NDERF will ask for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.

What NDERF  Will Do With Your Information. If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by NDERF and will only be used by NDERF to support your customer relationship with us. We will not add you to a mailing list, or newsletter without your registration for this service. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service.

What Others May Do With Your Information. NDERF does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your full name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time NDERF may use agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for NDERF (such as DATABASE MAINTENANCE, FURTHER EXAMPLES), however, they are required by us to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services for NDERF. 

#### Third Party Links

NDERF does allow links to and from other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave  WWW.NDERF.ORG, NDERF cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site. 

#### Changes to this Policy

NDERF may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.   
Contacting Us. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can write to:

  * NDERF
  * PO Box 20238
  * Houma, LA
  * 70360
